I hold my breath for a second because of your serious eyes.
From that moment, I can't ask you about anything.
Loneliness in stardust.
No doubt I'm unconsciously timid by cherishing the one I love.
I pretend not to see my teardrops.
How many more times will we two miss each other...
Original Work: Adachi Mitsuru
Serialized in Shonen Sunday
...and take a roundabout route before feeling each other?
Please touch. Touch. Touch this.
You touch and reach out to get a bouquet...
...in which only flowers of sighs were bundled.
I wish I weren't in love so that this loneliness...
...would go away before I know it.
Say "Hello" to sorrow in secret.
Theme Song: "Touch"
"If I'm Without You"
Composer/Arranger: Serizawa Hiroaki
Singer: Iwasaki Yoshimi
(Canyon Records)
Episode 01
No matter what anyone says
We're twins !!
Uesugi
Asakura
Punch
What nice weather!
Kacchan should be running
in the park right about now.
Morning, Minami.
Going out already?
I'm going to
clean the shop.
Waking up early and cleaning,
just like your dear departed mother.
What a great daughter!
Punch!
All right.
Just like Tacchan.
Morning!
Done with the morning chores.
Kacchan's back.
South Wind
Morning!
Here, a present for you
this morning, Minami.
From the Mom & Pop
vegetable store?
I can't believe it...
...whenever he sees me,
he just talks about the Koushien.
Hey!
He can't help it.
You're everyone's star of hope.
Out of everyone, you're the
one that expects the most.
Of course!
You promised me you'd
take me to the Koushien.
Don't worry.
I'll definitely take you.
Good!
I gotcha. I gotcha.
I'll take you, too.
Hey, you two...
...up this early
in the morning?
You two look good together.
Wait a sec, Father!
Don't say such weird things!
See ya.  I've got
morning practice.
A distinct head
and perfect grades.
He's the sportsman
of future generations.
We're counting on you,
next door neighbor.
I won't have to worry
when you're his wife.
Oh, such bliss.
South Wind
Hurry!  Hurry!
I have to go to school!
Right, right, right, right!
Kacchan, wait!
I'll go with you!
It's pretty early.
Why don't you take your time?
Nope, I want to
watch baseball practice.
That Tacchan...
Science
Uesugi Tatsuya
English, Math,
Japanese, Science.
That does it.
Thanks for waiting!
Hey!
Yeah!
Did Kazuya go to school yet?
He should've!
Is Tatsuya still sleeping?
He couldn't be sleeping.
He's always doing that.
Meisei Junior High School
Kazuya, you're wonderful!
So cool!
Keep it up!
Good! Good!
Great as usual!
Look over here!
All right, Kazuya!
Put 'er right here!
Here it comes.
Wonderful!
Junior High Math
Huh?
Minami?
Baseball
Club
Kazuya!
Have a good game!
We'll be cheering you on.
How's your arm?
Kacchan, it's hard
being popular, isn't it?
It's troublesome...
Safe!
You didn't break
your tardy record!
Shut up!
Oh, my.
Even in your shoe box.
What a hassle.
I'll pick them up for you.
Here, loverboy.
What about you, Tacchan?
Declaration
of Revenge
Declaration of revenge.
Thought so.
That's right!
Draw a line between two
angles and call it AB.
Call the diagonal C.
So the following theorem holds.
A squared plus
B squared = C squared.
Mr. Uesugi Kazuya
It's from Takizawa Youko
in class 2B, huh?
A cute girl
with pretty eyes.
All right. All right.
Ol' Tacchan will
take care of it.
Boys' Bathroom
All right.
Just like a twin.
I look just like Kazuya.
Uesugi, you came
for me, didn't you?
Hi!
No way!
Really?
I'm so lucky!
What's that?
Don't you have
baseball practice?
It's okay.
It's not necessary
for me to practice.
That's right.
You're a genius, after all.
When you get to high school,
will you play in the Koushien?
I wonder.
I'm not too
sure about that.
Rather than that,
I'm living life now.
You're pretty cute.
Oh, my.
What should I do?
Tacchan!
Yes!
What're you doing, Tacchan?
Let's go home.
Huh?
Tacchan?!
Hurry up!
It's okay! Let's go!
Tacchan?
Where did I goof up?
No matter how you look,
I'll still know it's you.
I see.
I thought
I looked like him.
Geez.
Hey!
What're you doing?!
Tacchan is Tacchan!
Kacchan is Kacchan!
Why're you mad?
You know Kazuya doesn't want
to see any girl other than you!
It's fine if you
leave me like this!
What's with her?
What's with...?!
Minami, you moron!
Uesugi
Those sweet memories of Paris.
Oh, Honey, we still
have memories of Paris.
Gotcha! Gotcha!
I'll clean this ear, too.
Oh, Honey!
All finished!
Stop it!
Tatsuya, are you just
gonna watch television?
Shouldn't you be studying with
Kazuya and Minami in the study room?
Yeah. Yeah.
Excuse me.
Gotcha!
Honey, hurry it up!
Our family, the Uesugi's, and the
family next door, the Asakura's...
...had three kids born
in the same year.
We've always been friends.
And very active.
I still think they're
restless, even for kids.
For Pete's sake.
One day, our parents
with their hands full...
All right, we'll put
our powers together.
Let's put the
kids together.
Yes, let's.
In between both houses...
...they pitched in and
made a house for us kids.
Quiet, isn't it?
Yes, quiet.
Truly.
At first, it was just
a place for us to play.
A few years later, its name
changed to the "study room."
Then we noticed that one of
the three of us was a girl.
It was at
about that time...
Meisei Junior High School
Safe!
Lucky guy, being surrounded
by girls so early in the morning!
Hey, Tatsuya.
We've been waiting.
We got a good book!
Wanna see?
Why do I gotta be
surrounded by guys?
Oh, come on.
Calm down. Calm down.
Uesugi!
Here.
What a cute cushion!
Will you do it for me?
What?
Give it to someone?
Yes.
To Kazuya.
It's a handmade cushion.
Please.
Now see here!
Give it to him directly!
That's no good.
It'd be bad if other
girls found out about it.
When you go home,
can you give it to Kazuya?
Please!
There's no point...
...no matter how much
you like Kazuya.
Why?
Kazuya's got Minami.
Just give up.
No way!
Asakura said she was only
Kazuya's childhood friend!
They're childhood friends...
...but not just that.
Tacchan!
Yes!
I...uh...
How're you gonna
make up for this?
Huh? About w...what?
Don't "about what" me!
What did you tell Yasuko?
Yasuko...
Oh, Yasuko with the
handmade cushion!
Don't "Oh!" me!
The girls are in an uproar because
of your irresponsible words!
Why're they in an uproar?
When did Kacchan and
I say we were engaged?
Oh, that.
That's right, though, isn't it?
It's a fact that that's what both of our parents want.
That has nothing
to do with this!
All real people
decide for themselves.
You don't like Kazuya?
It's not that
I don't like him.
Hey, you see...
...for the two of you,
and for everyone else...
...shouldn't you let it
happen out in the open?
Hey, now.
We haven't even planned
a wedding or anything!
There's no telling
what could happen!
I don't know what kind of
nice person Kacchan might meet.
There's no telling what type
of person I might start liking.
But if I go wrong somewhere...
...I could wind up getting
married to a weirdo like you!
Just...for example...
Hey, there you are!
You jerk!
Gimme back my book!
Okay, then?
Go explain it clearly to everyone.
You're so pretty.
Cute as usual, eh?
Yeah! Yeah!
Thanks!
If you mean the book,
it fell down on school grounds.
Yeah! Yeah...
I see.
Harada has it!
Pardon me!
Big Brother, thank you!
All right.
Here I go!
Ow, ow, ow!
You're not in shape.
When we get to high school,
you should join a club.
All right!
I'm in great shape.
Yeah!
Awesome, awesome!
Say, Kacchan,
what's this one?
Let's see. That's...
Oh, I see.
I'm disturbing your studies.
Good night.
What about this
wedding dress?
Look.
This is wonderful.
Where? Oh, Minami
would look great in this!
Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah.
But Kacchan's bridegroom
figure is really fine.
Those two are
the ideal couple.
I'm looking
forward to it.
Look.
This one's wonderful, too.
But if I go
wrong somewhere...
...I could wind up getting
married to a weirdo like you!
Just...for example...
For example, huh?
Mom!  Mom!
Where did my bag
that was here go?
I had it right by the door!
What're you fussing about?
Isn't it Sunday?
I've got practice!
Hurry and find it!
Okay.
Is this it?
Yeah, that's it!
Well, gotta go!
See you later!
What're you doing
sleeping in here?!
Couldn't help it.
My parents are
whining about...
...how Kazuya is always doing
his homework so great.
You saw, didn't you?
You're the one who
started to get undressed.
Pervert.
Moron.
A real pervert wouldn't have
coughed out loud until the end.
I see.
Shit!
So close!
Tacchan!
What is it?
Wanna go to the pool?
I bought a new swimsuit.
What am I,
Kazuya's pinch-hitter?
I won't force you to.
I understand.
It's a pain.
But, oh well...
...I'll go with you.
I shouldn't have coughed.
Hey, Minami...
...at the pool some beautiful
girl just starts talking to me.
Surprisingly, she's taken
an interest in me.
She asked if I wanted to play
baseball and told me I have talent.
Popular guys have
a hard time.
Tacchan, at least do the
previews seriously!
Sure!
Next time on Touch...
"A Woman's Intuition.
Tatsuya's Talent is on my mind."
It'll be interesting,
so watch it!
Okay?
How many summers have now passed by between us?
Tatsuya:
Kazuya:
Minami:
Mitsuya Yuji
Namba Keiichi
Hidaka Noriko
Koutarou:
Minami's Dad:
Mr. Uesugi:
Hayashiya Kobuhei
Masuoka Hiroshi
Chiba Shigeru
Without you, even a picture of the beach I took...
...when we were romping around...
...looks so monochromatic.
Koushien =
A baseball tournament held every year.
Basically the national championships.
It's held at the stadium by the same name.
A thing that time has left behind.
Translation:
Paul
Yutaka Sasagawa
Song Translation:
Yuko Wada
Listen, I get speechless every time I see you...
Timing:
Paul
Fred
Timing Edits:
Todd Perkins
Editing:
Paul
Ryder
Fred
Todd Perkins
Barbara
Dave
Lillian
Brain
...for I only want to tell you the truth.
Subtitled by:
NT-Anime
&
Central Anime(Kansas)
BD Version
Please stay here forever.
A postcard I forgot to send you falls deeply in my heart.
The one that says I love you.